# JOIVRE CHARLES

Full Stack Engineer

UI/UX Designer

Developer

## **PROFILE**

Full-Stack Developer who possesses exceptional communication and collective cooperation abilities which have developed from the client service industry. The integration of scientific and innovative experiences with my analytical and development capabilities has allowed success in collaboration on projects in teams of 3-5 developers. The excitement of sharing these problem-solving capabilities and constant yearning for knowledge are to some extent my key drivers.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### J.P. Morgan Chase ~ Miami, FI

#### Associate Banker ~ 12/2020 - Current

- Monitoring data entry to ensure accurate recording of client reports or invoices.
- Upheld strict financial controls to ensure accurate and secure transfer of finances.
- Assist clients processing transactions through computational methods

Apple ~ Miami, FI

#### Genius Administrator ~ 08/2015-08/2020

- Managed the repairs of 115 computers through perpetual examination of our internal databases.
- Organized and managed team of 21 technicians through numerous development workshops.
- Delivered ongoing feedback to ensure high efficiency repairs and favorable return of client devices.

## **PROJECTS**

 $\textbf{Map3ater} \rightarrow (\texttt{https://github.com/JimGigantes/Map3ater}) \mid (\texttt{https://gimgigantes.github.io/Map3ater/}) \mid (\texttt{https://github.com/JimGigantes/Map3ater}) \mid (\texttt{https:$ 

- A catalog of nations with their most popular cuisines. Allows you to discover a new dish from an international nation with a mealDB API. Each recipe added to your favorites is saved in your passport.
- o Built With: HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | Materialize |

#### Electro-City → (https://infinite-atoll-29760.herokuapp.com/)

- A site which allows users to post vintage items they no longer want and sell to which
  ever client feels the asking price for the item is equitable. Clients will be verified so
  there won't be risk of speaking to bots.
- o Built With: HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | Materialize | MERN | Recaptcha

#### Google Library → (https://sleepy-castle-98672.herokuapp.com/)

- This application utilizes the google books api to search for and display books the clients maybe interested in. These books are stored and can be referenced later if the client wants to review their collection at a later period.
- o Built With: HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | Materialize | MERN |

## CONTACT

**T** 

(786) 436-6082

M

astemcode@gmail.com

in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/joivre-charles-002b40127



www.astemcode.com ~ (Portfolio)



https://github.com/Astemcode

## SKILLS

## TOOLS

HTML5

Visual Studio Code

JavaScript

GitHub

CSS3

Heroku

mySQL

Robo3t

React

Git Bash

jQuery

Bootstrap

Agile Methodology

Materialize

MERN

Relational Databases

## **EDUCATION**

### **University of Miami**

August 2020 - March 2021 | (Miami, FI) Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

#### Florida International University

July 2020 | (Miami, FL)

Bachelor of Science in Biological Sciences

#### 4Geeks Academy

January - May 2020 | (Miami, FI)

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development